pretty dystopian how whenever there's issues that affect black or african people like no one cares
like literally no one i remember how like a few months ago it was trendy to care about congo now
like literally no one cares like at all and it's just kind of weird to me because like why is it
when it's us no one cares like we're at what seven million displaced and millions killed and nobody's
concerned this account right here papi orion is literally documenting this in real time on tiktok
so i've been following i've been interacting trying to do what i can in the link in his bio you can
literally donate and actually make a real tangible change like you can even choose what you want your
money to go towards it's not just like throwing your money in a crapshoot with no idea where it's
going you can literally pick what you want your money to go towards and just so y'all know i put
my money where my mouth is i've also been donating when i can so please go and follow this guy and
repost his stuff even if you don't have money to donate i feel like the negative two seconds it
takes to repost a video really is not that difficult
i feel like i'm giving you a little bit of money to help people out to help people out
you